

#### Contact



artemdanilow95@gmail.com



+48797667497

#### Skills

- HTML
- Css, Sass
- Tailwindcss
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- Next.js
- Alpine.js
- Strapi CMS
- Statamic CMS
- Figma
- Git

## Languages

- polish (C2)
- russian (C2)
- english (B1)

#### Hobby

- Tricking
- Sport gymnastics
- Travels

# Artem Danilov

## Frontend developer

#### About me

I have been writing code professionally for two years, and before starting my first job as a programmer, I spent one year at self-study. I can create fast and responsive pages with modern technologies. I have been learning new features all the time to provide the best solutions.

## **Experience**

#### 4DMIND

Frontend developer | 02.2021 - 02.2023

- Creating i editing web pages, using technologies such as: HTML, CSS, Javascript, TailwindCss, Alpine.js
- Creating reusable components
- Migration from the old to the new version of CMS
- Migration from other CMS
- Improvement performance and SEO
- Creating documentations
- Introducing customers to the system
- Support for customers from Poland and abroad

#### GRAWITACJA SPORT ACADEMY (EXTRA JOB)

Acrobatics instructor | 05.2018 - obecnie

- Teaching elements of acrobatics/gymnastics
- Conducting personal and group classes for children

### Education

#### POST-SECONDARY COLLEGE OF SPORT MEDICINE

Vocational education | 2017 - 2019

specialisation: Massage therapist

## Portfolio

#### 4DMIND.COM

The website of a Polish company specializing in digital products, where I had the pleasure to work. It is my first website that I built commercially as part of learning CMS Statamic.

#### HIGHLANDSOLUTIONS.COM

The website of a US company specializing in digital products. One of the nicest websites I have created. I was most satisfied with the parallax effect at the bottom of the page, even though it is not complicated.

#### RAPIDROBOTICS.COM

The website of a US company specializing in building industrial robots. The website was initially built in React, which had a negative impact on SEO. There were also a lot of animations that slowed down the website. The site was rewritten using CMS Statamic.

✓ I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).